Inventory of the Papers of Judge George H. Revercomb, 1971-1993
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Civil Cases-Opinions, Orders, Etc.
  - Connors v. Middle Fork Corp. 89-0698 (Box 42)
  - Connors v. Barrick Gold Exploration 89-3166 (Box 42)
  - Connors v. Island Creek Coal, Co. 86-0299 (Box 42)
  - Corbett v. Palmer 87-0784 (Box 42)
  - Consumers Union of U.S., Inc. v. Federal Reserve Board 89-3008 (Box 42)
  - Cooley v. U.S. Parole Commission 86-3390 (Box 42)
  - Copeland v. Morris 91-1150 (Box 42)
  - Corbett v. Palmer 87-0784 (Box 42)
  - Cotton v. Buckeye Gas Products Co. 85-2228 (Box 42)
  - Cox v. Sec'y of Labor 90-0340 (Box 42)
  - Crawford Fitting Co. v. Sec'y of the Navy 88-2496 (Box 42)
  - Crucible Materials Corp. v. Sumitomo Special Metals Co., Ltd 89-1170 (Box 42)
  - Crumpton v. D.C. 85-1613 (Box 42)
  - Cunningham v. United National Bank of Washington 88-1008 (Box 42)
  - D'Angelo v. U.S. Attorney General 91-1527 (Box 42)
  - Datacard Corp. v. Kunz KG. Kunz & Digital v. Datacard 90-1517 (Box 42)
  - Delgado v. Federal Bureau of Prisons 88-3691 (Box 42)
  - Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee v. Federal Election Commission 90-1504 (Box 42)
  - Dendy v. U.S. Department of the Interior (Box 42)
  - Dennis v. Meese 88-1538 (Box 42)
  - Dennis v. Montedonico 86-1043 (Box 42)
  - D.C. v. Westlind Construction Co. 86-2779 (Box 42)
  - D.C. Common Cause v. D.C. & Rivers 85-3528 (Box 42)
  - Doe v. Weinberger 85-1996 (Box 42)
  - Dole v. National Alliance of Postal and Federal Employees 89-2019 (Box 42)
  - Dorman v. Thornburgh 90-0614 (Box 42)
  - Dorsey v. Cavazos 88-1396 (Box 42)
  - Dorsey v. Check 88-1396 (Box 42)
  - Dover Administrative Services v. Riggs National Bank 88-0437 (Box 42)
  - Dr. Pepper/Seven Up Co. Inc. v. Federal Trade Commission 91-2712 (Box 42)
  - Dudley v. U.S. 88-1195 (Box 42)
  - Durnan v. U.S. Department of Commerce 90-2704 (Box 42)
  - EBM Group Corp., Ltd. v. Gulfstream Aerospace Corp. 92-1454 (Box 42)
  - Edens v. Musolino 88-2529 (Box 42)
  - Edmond v. U.S. Postal Service 88-0241 (Box 42)
  - Edmond v. U.S. Postal Service 88-0241 (Box 42)
  - Edwards v. Mutual of Omaha Insurance Co. 85-2347 (Box 42)
  - Ellis County, Texas v. U.S. 92-1110 (Box 42)
  - Emory v. Psychiatric Institutes of America 89-2181 (Box 42)
  - Epperly v. State of Alaska 89-0674 (Box 42)
  - Fairley v. Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co. 90-2446 (Box 42)
  - Farmer v. Mount Vernon Realty, Inc. 86-0931 (Box 42)
  - Federal Loan Mortgage Corp. v. Park Monroe Limited 89-0333 (Box 42)
  - First American Bank, NA. v. Corby-Lynn Real State Co. 91-356 (Box 42)
  - Fisher v. Dunkin 86-2014 (Box 42)
  - Flanagan v. Columbialand Ventures, Inc. 85-0346 (Box 42)
  - Fletcher v. Braxton 88-2866 (Box 42)
  - Fong v. U.S. Department of the Treasury 86-2297 (Box 42)
  - Foundation of Economics Trends v. Walkins 89-1483 (Box 42)
  - Franklin Asaph Limited Partnership v. Federal Deposit Insurance Corp. 91-1856 (Box 42)
  - Frazier v. University of D.C. 90-1062 (Box 42)
  - Frye v. U.S. Environmental Protection Agency 90-3041 (Box 42)
  - Fulani v. Brady 88-2649 (Box 42)
  - Fergussin v. D.C. Metropolitan Police Department 88-0432 (Box 42)
  - Gallagher v. Quigg 87-1259 (Box 42)
  - Garcia v. Yeutter 90-0981 (Box 42)
  - Garnett v. U.S. Soldiers & Airmen's Home 86-0432 (Box 42)
  - G.C. Services Corp. v. U.S. 86-0431 (Box 42)
  - Georgetown University v. Sportec International v. Tully Associates 88-1801 (Box 42)
  - Germany v. Operating Engineers Trust Fund of Washington, D.C. 91-1797 (Box 42)
  - Gersman v. Group Health Association, Inc. 88-1820 (Box 42)
  - Geske v. Attorney General 84-2954 (Box 42)
  - Globus v. Burnley 85-1582 (Box 42)
  - Globus v. Dole 85-1582 (Box 42)
  - Globus v. Skinner 8501582 (Box 42)
  - Gould v. Mitsui Mining and Smelting Co. Ltd. 91-1272 (Box 42)
  - Gordan v. Tish 85-0924 (Box 42)
  - Gordon v. Warner Corp. 86-2507 (Box 42)
  - Grant v. Bullock 87-1353 (Box 42)
  - Graham v. D.C. 92-0147 (Box 42)
  - Green v. Resolution Trust Corp. 92-0289 (Box 42)
  - Green v. Kinney Shop Corp. 88-0365 (Box 42)
  - Green v. Secretary of the Treasury 88-1926 (Box 43)
  - Greenpeace U.S. v. Mosbacher 88-2158 (Box 43)
  - Greenwood v. Seiko Instrumental and Electronics 87-1098 (Box 43)
  - Gregg v. Beta Construction Co. 84-2914 (Box 43)
  - Hanlon v. American Federation of Government Employees 86-2356 (Box 43)
  - Hanson v. Grennspan 91-1599 (Box 43)
  - Hanson v. Grennspan 91-1599 (Box 43)
  - Hardbower v. Zuckerman, Spalder, Goldstein 91-1579 (Box 43)
  - Harmon v. Meese 88-1766 (Box 43)
  - Harmon v. Plaut 89-1197 (Box 43)
  - Harmon v. Metpath 88-1181 (Box 43)
  - Hastings Condominium Association v. National Bank of Washington 86-1350 (Box 43)
  - Healthcare San Antonio, Inc. v. Mendez 90-0845 (Box 43)
  - Henderson v. Lujan 91-1356 (Box 43)
  - Henthorn v. Department of the Navy 91-3149 (Box 43)
  - Henthorn v. National Transportation Safety Board 90-2943 (Box 43)
  - Henthorn v. Lawn 90-2858 (Box 43)
  - Henthorn v. Quinlan 90-3116 (Box 43)
  - Hill v. U.S. Parole Commission 90-1050 (Box 43)
  - Hill v. U.S. Board of Parole 90-0897 (Box 43)
  - Hinton v. Metropolitan Police Department 5th District 89-2784 (Box 43)
  - Hockman v. U.S. v. Dawson Brothers 89-1466 (Box 43)
  - Holland v. Board of Trustees of University of D.C. 90-1703 (Box 43)
  - Holland v. CIA 91-1233 (Box 43)
  - Holt v. Valencia 86-1864 (Box 43)
  - Hudnell v. Co-Op Investment Bankers 86-2524 (Box 43)
  - Hunter v. Meese 86-1864 (Box 43)
  - Hunter-Bey v. Bureau of Prisons 87-2536 (Box 43)
  - Hurd v. New England Mutual Life Insurance Co. 85-2901 (Box 43)
  - I.A.M. National Pension Fund v. Pepsico, Inc. 86-2881 (Box 43)
  - IBM Credit Corp. v. Railing Corp. v. Hayman Construction 88-3440 (Box 43)
  - Ingram v. First American Bank 88-2585 (Box 43)
  - Institute for Policy Studies v. Department of Air Force 87-0916 (Box 43)
  - Ingram v. First American Bank 88-2585 (Box 43)
  - International Brotherhood of Painters & Allied Trades Union v. Rose Brothers Home Decorating Center, Inc. 91-1699 (Box 43)
  - International Transcription Services, Inc. v. U.S. 90-3129 (Box 43)
  - ITPE-MEBA/NMU FUNDS v. United International Investigative Services 90-0066 (Box 43)
  - Jackson v. American Chemical Society 90-2817 (Box 43)
  - James Electrical Control, Inc. v. American Insurance Co. 87-0363 (Box 43)
  - Jenkins v. Leventhal 89-3318 (Box 43)
  - Johnson v. Greater Southeast Community Hospital Corp. 90-1992 (Box 43)
  - Johnson v. Quinlan 90-1992 (Box 43)
  - Johnson v. U.S. 88-3003 (Box 43)
  - Joyce v. Anly Construction Corp. 89-2246 (Box 43)
  - Joyce v. Clyde Sandoz Masonry Contractors 87-1894 (Box 43)
  - Kareem Abdul-Jabbar v. Begg, Inc. 86-0944 (Box 43)
  - Kassatly v. Yazbeck 88-3218 (Box 43)
  - Kasmir v. Carey International, Inc. 88-3218 (Box 43)
  - Kaushiva v. Board of Trustees of the University of D.C. 87-2517 (Box 43)
  - Kayfirst Corp. v. Washington Terminal Co. 91-404 (Box 43)
  - Kearing v. Guinee 90-0149 (Box 43)
  - Kearing v. Madigan 90-2804 (Box 43)
  - Kennedy v. Kennedy 89-1408 (Box 43)
  - Kenner v. U.S. Parole Commission 90-1310 (Box 43)
  - Kenney v. Roland Parson Contracting Co. 91-1230 (Box 43)
  - Khan v. Hershman 87-2868 (Box 43)
  - King v. Kao 88-1500 (Box 43)
  - Kirke-Van Orsdel, Inc. v. Smith-Sternau Organization, Inc. 90-712 (Box 43)
  - Kirkland v. District of Columbia 92-0076 (Box 43)
  - Kleiman v. U.S. Department of Energy 90-0251 (Box 43)
  - Knight v. Department of Defense 87-480 (Box 43)
  - Knox v. U.S. 89-0548 (Box 43)
  - Kovacs v. Thornburgh 90-0159 Kreis v. Sec'y of the Air Force 85-1169 (Box 43)
  - Kuntz v. New York State Board of Elections 92-2009 (Box 43)
  - Lawson v. Nevada Power Co. 90-0749 (Box 43)
  - Lawrence v. Braxton 88-2220 (Box 43)
  - Lee v. Brady 87-0977 (Box 43)
  - Leeds v. Mosbacher 89-1857 (Box 43)
  - Leeds v. Quigg 89-1925 (Box 43)
  - Lemere v. Burnley 87-1506 (Box 43)
  - Lewis v. Stempson 90-0592 (Box 43)
  - Liberty Lobby Inc v. Reis 84-3452 (Box 43)
  - Lindholm v. U.S. 92-2136 (Box 43)
  - Lipsman d/b/a ADL Financial Services v. Global Environment Corp. 89-2637 (Box 43)
  - Lisee v. CIA 89-1266 (Box 43)
  - Lockley v. Chao 91-1345 (Box 43)
  - Lofton v. Roskens 87-3032 (Box 43)
  - Lombrado v. U.S. Department of Justice 87-2652 (Box 43)
  - Loveless v. Armstrong World Industries 86-1970 (Box 43)
  - Lowry v. Reagan 87-2196 (Box 43)
  - Lu-Ann Bakery Shop, Inc. v. Nelson 88-1120 (Box 43)
  - Lufkin v. Director, Executive Office for U.S. Attorneys 85-1959 (Box 43)
  - Macht v. Skinner 89-1161 (Box 44)
  - MacPherson v. Searle & Co. & Meck 90-0095 (Box 44)
  - Magee v. Thornburgh 90-0377 (Box 44)
  - Makel v. Williams 88-1568 (Box 44)
  - Males v. Sullivan 89-0521 (Box 44)
  - Marine Management, Inc. v. 23' Goliff Sailboat 86-0741 (Box 44)
  - Martin v. Stone 90-1596 (Box 44)
  - Mathis-Bay v. U.S. Attorney General 86-3210 (Box 44)
  - May v. Board of Trustees of the University of D.C. 84-1849 (Box 44)
  - MBL International Contractors, Inc. v. Republic of Trinidad and Tobago 89-1003 (Box 44)
  - McAffee v. Clerk of the Supreme Court Spagnolo 88-1933 (Box 44)
  - McAffee v. Reagan 88-0398 (Box 44)
  - McCarter v. Bowen 87-1256 (Box 44)
  - McCullough v. McPherson 90-2365 (Box 44)
  - McDaniels v. Howard University 89-3228 (Box 44)
  - McDuffus v. U.S. 85-3083 (Box 44)
  - McGovern v. AIWA American 85-2890 (Box 44)
  - McNeal v. Hi-Lo Powered Scaffolding, Inc. 84-2561 (Box 44)
  - Meisel v. Rohrbau GmBH & Co. v. Department of the Army 87-1266 (Box 44)
  - Mergentime Corp. v. Washington Metropolitan Area Transportation Authority ["Metro Green Line"] 89-1055 (Box 44)
  - Michigan Citizens for an Independent Press v. Attorney General of the U.S. 88-2322 (Box 44)
  - Milam v. Justice Department 87-3322 (Box 44)
  - Milam v. Harps 87-3431 (Box 44)
  - Milam v. Wade 87-3429 (Box 44)
  - Mil-Com Electronics Corp. v. Aldridge 89-0095 (Box 44)
  - Miller v. Amalgamated Casualty Co. 87-1204 (Box 44)
  - Miller v. Baker 90-409 (Box 44)
  - Moore v. Cooper 88-3573 (Box 44)
  - Monleone v. Sullivan 89-2526 (Box 44)
  - Montavlo, Cordero, Matsuzaki v. Thornburgh 90-2714 (Box 44)
  - Montgomery v. Hodges 90-0440 (Box 44)
  - Morabito v. Beggiani 89-0293 (Box 44)
  - Mueller v. U.S. District Court of Penn 89-0009 (Box 44)
  - Munn v. U.S. 91-2158 (Box 44)
  - Napoleon-Bey v. Plaut 87-1147 (Box 44)
  - Nathan v. WMATA 85-0214 (Box 44)
  - National Association of Letter Carriers, AFL-CIO v. Reagan 86-0866 (Box 44)
  - National Association of Rehabilitation Services, Inc. v. Bowen 86-2686 (Box 44)
  - National Bank of Washington v. Akhavan 87-1540 (Box 44)
  - National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association v. Burnley 88-0485 (Box 44)
  - National Treasury Employees Union v. Golden 85-3881 (Box 44)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation v. Dole 85-6182 (Box 44)
  - Nautilius Insurance Co. v. Dolphn Pools Corp. 89-3394 (Box 44)
  - Nelson v. U.S. Department of Justice, FBI 87-1833 (Box 44)
  - New York State Ophthalmological Society v. Bowen 86-1926 (Box 44)
  - Nunez v. S/T Evmits Navigating Co. 86-1926 (Box 44)
  - Overholt v. McDaniel 90-1681 (Box 44)
  - Packer v. Garrett 89-3431 Painting & Drywall Work Preservation Fund Inc. v. U.S. Department of Housing 86-2431 (Box 44)
  - Patlex Corp. v. Quigg 86-3294 (Box 44)
  - Payne v. WMATA 89-0387 (Box 44)
  - Pederson v. Leroy 87-0979 (Box 44)
  - Pennsylvania Ave. Development Corp. v. One Parcel in D.C. 87-2127 (Box 44)
  - Peskowitz v. Mount Vernon Realty, Inc. 86-0931 (Box 44)
  - Pettiford v. D.C. 91-1689 (Box 44)
  - Pittman v. Ridley (Box 44)
  - Poole v. Smithsonian Museum of Natural History Bookstore 91-517 (Box 44)
  - Potomac Valley Brick v. Gibbons 85-0822 (Box 44)
  - Potter v. Department of the Navy 88-1850 (Box 44)
  - Pringle v. Howard University 87-0883 (Box 44)
  - Progressive Cellular Associates v. Monroe 87-3077 (Box 44)
  - Prost v. Thrifty Rent-A-Car System, Inc. 86-0263 (Box 44)
  - Prudential Insurance Co. of America v. Baskin & Steingut, P.C. 85-3527 (Box 44)
  - Psychiatric Institute of Washington, D.C. v. Wells 92-1416 (Box 44)
  - Public Citizen v. Burke 86-1787 (Box 44)
  - Qadir v. U.S. 89-1486 (Box 44)
  - Quality Brands, Inc. v. Barry 88-1999 (Box 44)
  - Ragusa v. Carlson 86-2347 (Box 44)
  - Ransom v. Goodyear Tire & Rubber Co. 87-0075 (Box 44)
  - Rao v. U.S. Agency for International Development 87-0021 (Box 44)
  - Reback v. Parsons 90-0348 (Box 45)
  - Rees v. Family Activities Center 89-0348 (Box 45)
  - Reeve Aleutian Airways v. U.S. 88-897 (Box 45)
  - Resolution Trust Corp. v. Bildman 91-632 Resolution Trust Corp. v. West 91-2922 Retirement & Security Program v. Oglethorpe Power Corp. 88-0279 (Box 45)
  - Reuber v. Stauffer Chemical Co. 84-0933 (Box 45)
  - Richards v. U.S. Merit Systems Protection Board 89-1041 (Box 45)
  - Richburg v. The Times Journal Co. 91-2805 (Box 45)
  - Ricks v. Simons 90-0249 (Box 45)
  - Roberts v. Smith 90-2078 (Box 45)
  - Robinson v. Carlucci 88-0049 (Box 45)
  - Robinson v. Garrett 88-2903 (Box 45)
  - Robinson v. Mount Vernon Realty Co. 86-931 (Box 45)
  - Robinson v. Sutter 92-2049 (Box 45)
  - Rochon v. U.S. Department of Justice 87-2239 (Box 45)
  - Rodriguez v. Resolution Trust Corp. 91-2998 (Box 45)
  - Rogers v. Nathan 89-2218 (Box 45)
  - Rowe v. Kidd & Congressional Quarterly, Inc. 88-3277 (Box 45)
  - Royal Tours v. International Travel Consultants, Inc. 88-0185 (Box 45)
  - Rubins Contractors, Inc. v. Lumbermens Mutual Insurance Co. 85-1235 (Box 45)
  - Rueda-Gomez v. Thornburgh 88-0692 (Box 45)
  - Ryan v. Brady 91-0608 (Box 45)
  - Saleh v. Braxton 92-0517 (Box 45)
  - Sabin v. Regardie, Regardie & Bartow 91-1891 (Box 45)
  - Sanders v. H & M Enterprises 88-3661 (Box 45)
  - Sawyer v. Porreca 91-912 (Box 45)
  - Schaefer v. Cheney 89-1850 (Box 45)
  - Schalk v. Reagan 87-2298 (Box 45)
  - Schlick v. Sullivan 90-2505 (Box 45)
  - Scott v. U.S. Parole Commission 91-2838 (Box 45)
  - Secord v. Cockburn 88-0727 (Box 45)
  - Sen-Tung v. U.S. 90-2534 (Box 45)
  - Dendy v. U.S. Department of Interior 87-0906 (Box 45)
  - Secord v. Wheaton 88-533 (Box 45)
  - Shamey v. Administrator, General Services Administration 87-1491 (Box 45)
  - Shamloo v. Lifespring, Inc. 88-2932 (Box 45)
  - Silvions v. Federal Bureau of Prisons 87-2799 (Box 45)
  - Silva v. U.S. 92-0391 (Box 45)
  - Silvas v. WMATA 90-1724 (Box 45)
  - Simmons v. Billington 88-2106 (Box 45)
  - Simmons v. Fulwood 89-2853 (Box 45)
  - Simmons v. Kora & Williams Corp. 88-3493 (Box 45)
  - Simmons v. Marsh 89-0448 (Box 45)
  - Simpson v. D.C. Metropolitan Police 92-0022 (Box 45)
  - Singletary v. Innerbichler 91-1962 (Box 45)
  - Slaughter v. Allright Parking, Inc. 90-1968 (Box 45)
  - Slater v. Quigg 85-2736 (Box 45)
  - Smallwood v. D.C. Board of Parole 87-1452 (Box 45)
  - Smith v. Quinlan 91-1187 (Box 45)
  - Smith v. Sullivan 89-2386 (Box 45)
  - Solaris International Corp. v. Hacker-Pschoorr Bran GMBH 88-2360 (Box 45)
  - Sorrells v. Elli Lilly & Co. 89-2073 (Box 45)
  - Southern Technologies, Inc. v. U.S. 90-1868 (Box 45)
  - Southland Corp. v. Goddette 91-999 (Box 45)
  - Spergel v. Dolphin Pools Corp. 89-0480 (Box 45)
  - SRS Technologies Corp. v. Department of Air Force 89-0464 (Box 45)
  - Stanley v. Plaut 87-2245 (Box 45)
  - State Department Federal Credit Union v. The Gas Screw Vessel "Selina II" 87-3083 State of Louisiana Department of Health v. Bowen 87-1330 (Box 45)
  - State of Louisiana Department of Health v. Sullivan 90-2231 (Box 45)
  - Staudinger v. Lotus Scientific Development 86-1157 (Box 45)
  - In re St. Charles Preservation Investors, Ltd. 89-3302 Steinberger v. Sun Refining & Marketing Co. 90-1157 (Box 45)
  - Stewart v. Capital Area Permanent Medical Group 89-1116 Stiglich v. Tracks, D.C., Inc. 88-2795 (Box 45)
  - Stone v. Williams & Connelly 92-0042 (Box 45)
  - Strang v. U.S. Arms Control & Disarment Agency 86-1057 (Box 45)
  - Summer v. U.S. Department of Justice 89-3300 (Box 45)
  - Summers v. U.S. Department of State 86-3230 (Box 45)
  - Survival Technology v. Marsh 89-2074 (Box 45)
  - Swisher v. Schneiderman 88-0146 (Box 45)
  - Skyes v. D.C. 87-863 (Box 45)
  - Tao v. Sessions 92-0144 (Box 45)
  - Tate v. Burke 90-1357 (Box 45)
  - Thomas v. Baker 87-1606 (Box 45)
  - Thomas v. D.C. 88-1932 (Box 45)
  - Thomas v. Braxton 92-1971 (Box 45)
  - Thomas v. General Services Administration 86-0941 (Box 45)
  - Thomas v. Saint Elizabeth's Hospital 89-2068 (Box 45)
  - Thomas v. WMATA 86-2605 (Box 45)
  - Thomas v. Schultz 86-2850 (Box 45)
  - Tobey v. National Labor Relations Board 92-413 (Box 45)
  - Tompkins v. Standard Federal Savings & Loan Association 86-3222 (Box 45)
  - Thompson v. U.S. 90-1658 (Box 45)
  - Turner v. Lumadue 90-1667 (Box 45)
  - Vithoven v. Thuss 91-0011 (Box 45)
  - Unimed, Inc. v. Quigg 88-2480 (Box 45)
  - United Mine Workers of America International Union v. Arch Mineral Corp. 92-0742 (Box 45)
  - U.S. v. Airline Tariff Publishing Co. 92-2864 (Box 45)
  - U.S. v. Becon Services Corp. & Aetna Casualty 91-2502 (Box 45)
  - U.S. v. Jack 88-0083 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Trimmel 91-155 (Box 46)
  - Valentine v. U.S. 87-3289 (Box 46)
  - Vance v. American Security Bank 87-1705 (Box 46)
  - Viehe v. Schools 84-3169 (Box 46)
  - Vietnam v. Veterans of America v. Secretary of the Navy 85-3208 (Box 46)
  - Wagner Seed Co., Inc. v. Bush 88-1922 (Box 46)
  - Walden v. Bush 88-3385 (Box 45)
  - Walden v. 100th Congress of the U.S. 89-0085 (Box 46)
  - Walker v. American National Red Cross 92-1405 (Box 46)
  - Walsh v. Dun & Bradstreet 90-0356 (Box 46)
  - Warrinder v. U.S. Marshalls Service 90-1669 (Box 46)
  - Waschitzki v. Vista International (D.C.) 87-0512 (Box 46)
  - Washington-El v. Thornburgh 89-0784 (Box 46)
  - Washington Hospital Center Corp. v. Waters 91-1638 (Box 46)
  - D.W.S. Washington Holdings, Inc. v. Jackson 88-3652 (Box 46)
  - Washington Tour Guides Association v. National Park Service 92-2074 (Box 46)
  - Whatley v. Barry 89-1385 (Box 46)
  - Wemhaff v. Tramps Management, Inc. 85-2140 (Box 46)
  - Western Residential, Inc. v. Resolution Trust Corp. 91-2751 (Box 46)
  - Wiley v. Bowen 91-5497 (Box 46)
  - Williams v. D.C. Board of Parole 88-1924 (Box 46)
  - Willens v. National Security Council 85-1400 (Box 46)
  - Williams v. WMATA 88-1901 (Box 46)
  - WMATA v. One Parcel 87-2774 (Box 46)
  - Young v. Secretary of Health 88-0004 (Box 46)
  - Young v. Martin Marietta Aerospace 86-1552 (Box 46)
  - Young v. Sullivan 89-2227 (Box 46)
  - Yuen v. Melvin 87-0115 (Box 46)
- Criminal Cases--Opinions, Orders, Etc.
  - U.S. v. Abrea 90-211 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Babb 90-571 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Blount 90-142-01 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Brockenborough 87-428 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Clarke 91-0195 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Cherry 91-248 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Cole 89-0022
  - U.S. v. Coulthrust 90-355 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Crosby 91-0559 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Frankel 90-0081 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Friedrick 86-0188 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Gibbs 88-0081-03 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Hagler 87-446-01 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Hawkins 87-446-04 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Hines 88-0022 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Huggins 90-0041 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Johnson 87-373 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Koonce 86-58-01 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Miller 88-0241 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Murphy 86-0435 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Randolph 91-366 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Recognition Equipment, Inc. 88-0385 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Sensi 86-0318 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Shabazz 90-0132 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Taylor 88-50 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Webb 89-131-03 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. White 91-0938 (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. Williams-Davis ["R St. Crew"] 91-0559-01, 02, 04, 06, 20 [see also Box 10] (Box 46)
  - Photographs of unidentified murdered women. [Linda Lazarus, an attorney whose name is on the envelope, is mentioned in the case file for Graham v. Durham and WMATA] n.d. (Box 46)
- Miscellany
  - Revercomb, George H.: Competency Determinations in the Criminal Justice System: A Trial Judge's Perspective. Dissertation for the degree of LL.M. in the Judicial Process at the University of Virginia (Box 47)
  - Revercomb, George H.: Opinions. Published in the years 1987-1990. St. Paul, Minnesota, West Publishing Company, 1986-1990 (Box 47)
  - The Judges' Journal. A Quarterly of the Judicial Administration Division. ABA, Vol. 23, No. 4 Vol. 24, Nos. 1-3 (Box 47)
  - 1984 Annual Report. District of Columbia Courts (Box 47)
  - Two subject index card boxes (Box 47)
  - Framed caricature sketch of Judge Revercomb during "R" St. Trial, given to him by defense counsel (Box 47)
  - Photographs
    - Sorrell, Clyde H. n.d.
    - Revercomb, George H. 1970
    - Revercomb, George 1992